公立学校教师的
There's a very high degree of turnover
流动率非常高。
among public school teachers.
因为生活条件是如此困难，
Because the conditions of life are
坦率地说是如此令人心碎。
so difficult and  frankly so heartbreaking.
当你怀着一颗饱满的心
And one of the things that
进入一个行业时，就会发生这样的事情，
happens when you go into a profession with a full heart.
这也是进入教学领域的唯一原因。
And that's the only reason to go into teaching.
你进去不是为了变得富有和出名。
You don't go in to get rich and famous.
就是那些压迫性的环境
It's that those oppressive conditions
会让你心碎。
then break your heart.
如果你没有某种支持，
And it's very hard to bear that,
就很难承受这种情况。
if you don't have some kind  of support.
在我看来，
It seems to me that there's
当我们不能支持
a kind of madness in any institution to fail,
从事这项工作的人的心时，
when we fail to support the
任何机构都会失败至极。
hearts of the people doing the work.
而相反，让他们受制于外部标准，
And instead, subject them to external standards,
受制于惩罚，为完成工作而责备他们。
to punishments, berate them for a job for it done.
当然，我们都知道，在一些非常基本的层面上，
Surely, we all know at some very basic level
为了发展我们所做的任何工作，
that to grow whatever work we doing,
我们需要有人照顾，
we need to be tended the way
就像园丁照料植物那样。
a gardener tends plants.
而这正是我认为公立学校教师需要的。
And that's what I think public school teacher's need.
但他们没有得到这种照顾。
But are not getting.
相反，他们受到了斥责，
They are getting instead berated
他们被指责为有各种
and they are getting accused of all kinds of
不足之处和能力缺失。
inadequacies and in competencies.
我们经常在报纸上看到这种情况。
We read it in the newspapers all the time.
结果很自然，人们放弃了，
And the result is very natural,  people bail out,
他们寻找让他们更快乐、
they look for something that makes them happier,
更满意的东西。
that's more satisfying.
但我不认为他们会高兴地退出,
But I don't think they bail out gladly,
我认为他们是悲哀地退出的，
I think they bail out sadly,
我觉得他们一开始是去教书的,
I think they went into teaching in the first place,
因为他们喜欢孩子，喜欢学习生活。
because they love kids and they love the learning life.
对他们中的许多人来说，这是一种悲哀，
And it's a grief for many of them,
在他们希望或
that they have to come to the end of the road
渴望这样做之前，
long before they had
他们不得不走到道路的尽头。
wished or desired to do so.